# Anthony Burke-Hall

anthonybhall1@gmail.com | 321-987-4043 | Palm Bay, FL | LinkedIn | GitHub | Portfolio

## SUMMARY

Passionate Frontend Web Developer with a keen eye for design and a drive to create engaging user experiences. Utilizing an agile methodology to reach development deadlines. Using Microsoft Teams to communicate with teammates in an agile environment. And to deliver the project smoothly by writing clean code that is effective and functional.

## **EXPERIENCE**

INVESTCLOUD | JR. FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER | Tampa, FL | Mar 2022 - Mar 2023

- Collaborated with 8 team members to identify site objectives and user needs, using Microsoft Teams and creating user-friendly website experiences with 15% more engagement
- Performed quality assurance (QA) checks on average per project, discovering bugs and communicating concerns to other designers, improving efficiency and user experience throughout the life cycle of a project
- Focused on building site functionality with HTML, CSS, and tracking tickets with Jira Orchestrated a seamless project management process by implementing an agile workflow; conducted daily stand-ups, sprint reviews, and retrospectives that reduced development time by 20% and increased client satisfaction by 35%
- Pushed code base with Tortoise SVN (Version control), to move tested code to the project

## COMPSYS | PRODUCTION TECH | Melbourne, FL | Oct 2020 - Mar 2022

- Working with a team to reach deadlines
- Producing materials at company standards
- Adapting to changing company needs to make projected customer needs
- Operate fiberglass production tools
- Monitor quality control
- Maintain equipment and workspace

## BUFFALO WILD WINGS | LINE COOK | Melbourne, FL | Feb 2016 - Mar 2019

- Followed OSHA( Occupational Safety and Health Administration) standards
- Communicated with the front of the house to deliver food safely and promptly to customers
- Organized kitchen staff to perform tasks effectively and orderly throughout their shift

# **EDUCATION**

BAYSIDE HIGHSCHOOL | DIPLOMA Palm Bay, FL | Aug 2011 - Jun 2015 GPA: 3.2

## **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- JQUERY
- BOOTSTRAP
- GITHUB
- NODEJS
- NPM
- MongoDB

- API
- SQL
- DATABASES
- SYSTEM PERFORMANCE
- BEHAVIOR MANAGEMENT
- OBJECT-ORIENTED METHODOLOGIES
- JSON

# **PROJECTS**

## TO-DO-LIST | Link

This full-stack app was designed with CSS, HTML, and JavaScript for the front end. And the backend, NodeJS, EJS & Express.Js were utilized. The user can add items to a list using Embedded JavaScript(EJS).

## PLAY THE DRUMS | Link

It was built with HTML, CSS & JavaScript. Demonstrates using event on-clicks with jQuery that plays sounds based on key clicks or buttons clicked on the website.

# DICE GAME | Link

This frontend application utilizes jQuery to create the logic to randomize the dice roll when the user clicks the button. And also changes the font to match the result of the dice roll.

# NEWSLETTER | Link

Full-stack app that incorporates CSS, HTML, JavaScript, and Node.js with the API from Mail chimp to create an email list web application.

# TINDOG (Tinder Clone) | Link

Tindog is a beautiful landing page for a mock Tinder landing page. This website was created with CSS, HTML, and Bootstrap. And demonstrates the elegant design of a modern landing page that can help drive sales.